So this video you're about to watch is my homie Libre X and he is coming to you from Palestine.
I know that it is in Espanol because he is Puerto Rican. However, I hope that you will take the time
to read the captions because he is sharing some very important information about Sudan and the Congo.
The Arab Emirates were stealing organs during the genocide in Al-Fashir.
On top of that, the United States is directly involved in the genocide that is happening in Sudan and we have evidence.
My homie, I'm Libre and I'm in Borussia and Gaza and today we are going to talk about Sudan and a chinching about Congo.
The Sudanese forces returned territory that was previously encountered by the RSF
refrigerators of organs that give more evidence to our claims that they were stealing organs from the Sudanese
that they were massacring in Al-Fashir.
In addition, the SAF had stolen planes from Steven Steven, a United States veteran.
Cut out the corporate middlemen and purchase my music directly from me.
Head to amandadiva.bandcamp.com and pay whatever price you want for Truth Translator.
This ain't a movement, it's movement music.